http://www.keystonervcenter.com/privacy

MENU
Home
Show Me RVs
Shop By Brand
Arctic Wolf & Alpha WolfCherokeeCoachmen ApexCoachmen CatalinaCoachmen Chaparral & BrookstoneCoachmen Galleria & BeyondFlagstaffGeorgetown Class AJayco LuxuryJayco Jay Flight, White Hawk & Feather, Octane & Toy HaulersPalomino ColumbusPrime Time CrusaderR-Pod, No-Bo & SurveyorSalem, FSX & Cruise LiteSalem HemisphereSierraSunseekerThor Motor CoachRogue Vengeance Toy HaulersVibe
New RVsValue RVsLeftover SaleBunkhouse Blowout
Teach Me RV!
Keystone RV SchoolCatalina InsiderGeorgetown Central
Contact UsGet FinancedFix My RVNeed A Part
Online Parts StoreParts Request
Community OutreachInternational Sales
AustraliaCanadaEuropeKorea & ChinaLatin America
About
StaffJob ListingsTestimonials & Reviews
Search
Keyword(s) or Stock #
Price Range
Price (low)
Price (high)
Condition
Any
New
Used
Dry Weight
Weight (low)
Weight (high)
Brand/Model
AnyCoachmenCoachmen: ApexCoachmen: Apex NanoCoachmen: BrookstoneCoachmen: Catalina Legacy EditionCoachmen: Catalina SummitCoachmen: Catalina Trail BlazerCoachmen: ChaparralForest RiverForest River: Alpha WolfForest River: Arctic WolfForest River: CherokeeForest River: Cherokee Grey WolfForest River: Cherokee Wolf PupForest River: Flagstaff ClassicForest River: Flagstaff Classic Super LiteForest River: Flagstaff E-ProForest River: Flagstaff Micro LiteForest River: Flagstaff ShamrockForest River: Flagstaff Super LiteForest River: Georgetown 5 Series GT5Forest River: Georgetown 7 Series GT7Forest River: No BoundariesForest River: R-PodForest River: SalemForest River: Salem Cruise LiteForest River: Salem FSXForest River: Salem HemisphereForest River: Salem Hemisphere Hyper-LyteForest River: SierraForest River: SunseekerForest River: Sunseeker LEForest River: SurveyorForest River: Surveyor LegendForest River: Vengeance RogueForest River: Vengeance Rogue ArmoredForest River: VibeJaycoJayco: EagleJayco: Eagle HTJayco: Jay FeatherJayco: Jay Feather MicroJayco: Jay FlightJayco: Jay Flight OctaneJayco: Jay Flight SLXJayco: North PointJayco: White HawkPrime TimePrime Time: CrusaderThor Motor CoachThor Motor Coach: Four Winds
Unit Type
AnyClass AClass CExpandable TrailerFifth WheelToy HaulerTravel Trailer
Year Range
Year (low)
Year (high)
Length Range
Length (low)
Length (high)
Search
Privacy Policy
class-a
Class A
class-b
Class B/B+
class-c
Class C
Travel Trailers
Privacy Policy (PDF)
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Al-Mar RV, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.keystonervcenter.com website ("Site").
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, social security number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Al-Mar RV, Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our Site: We may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Electronic newsletters
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Al-Mar RV, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
Mon - Fri: 8:00am - 6:00pmSat: 8:00am-5:00pmRV Parts & ServiceMon - Fri: 8:00am - 6:00pmSat: 8:00am - 4:00pm
Social Media
Contact Us
